<resources>
    <string name="app_name">coordinatorLayout</string>
    <string name="lorem">In the Google I/O 15, Google released a new support library which implements several components closely related with the Material Design\'s spec, among these components you can find new ViewGroups like the AppbarLayout, CollapsingToolbarLayout and CoordinatorLayout.\\nWell combined and configured these Viewgroups can be very powerful, therefore I have decided to write a post with some configurations and tips.\\nCoordinatorLayout\\n\\tAs its name suggests, the goal and philosophy of this ViewGroup is to coordinate the views that are inside it.\\nIn this example you can see how the views are coordinated with each other, with a glance, we can see how some Views depend on other. (we\'ll talk about this later). The AppBarLayout in this case is the blue view, placed under the collapsing image, it contains a Toolbar, a LinearLayout with title and subtitle and a TabLayout with some tabs.\\nWe can manage the behavior of direct childs in an AppbarLayout with the parameter: layout_scrollFlags. The value: scroll in this case it\'s present in almost all views, if it wasn\'t specified in any child then the childs of the AppbarLayout will remain static allowing the scrollable content slide behind it.\\nWith the value: snap, we avoid fall into mid-animation-states, this means that the animations will always hide or expand all the height of its view.\\nThe LinearLayout which contains the title and subtitle will be shown always that the user scrolls up, (enterAlways value), and the TabLayout will be always visible because we don\'t have any flag on it.\\nAppbarLayout flags\\nSCROLL_FLAG_ENTER_ALWAYS: When entering (scrolling on screen) the view will scroll on any downwards scroll event, regardless of whether the scrolling view is also scrolling.\\nSCROLL_FLAG_ENTER_ALWAYS_COLLAPSED: An additional flag for \'enterAlways\' which modifies the returning view to only initially scroll back to it\'s collapsed height.\\nSCROLL_FLAG_EXIT_UNTIL_COLLAPSED: When exiting (scrolling off screen) the view will be scrolled until it is \'collapsed\'.\\nSCROLL_FLAG_SCROLL: The view will be scroll in direct relation to scroll events.\\nSCROLL_FLAG_SNAP: Upon a scroll ending, if the view is only partially visible then it will be snapped and scrolled to it\'s closest edge.</string>
</resources>
